E. P. Dutton & Company, Inc. Records
E. P. Dutton & Company, Inc. Records
- Production files
  - Learning - Little (Box 20)
    Little Hercules - Frank Gruber Fall '65
    Little League Champions - Olgin
    The Little Medelaine
  - Little - Lucky (Box 20)
    The Little Ones
    Lonely Challenge
    The Lonely Graves
    The Long Wind
    The Longs of Louisiana - Opotowsky
    Look Toward the Sea - Frank Baines
    Love In Action - Henriques
    Love Taps Gently
    Lucky Days
  - Lutie - Man (Box 20)
    Lutie
    Madeline Young Wife
    Magic - Bouisson
    Make Way For The Music
    The Man Behind You - Bode
    The Man of the End Of the Rope - Townend
    Man, Rockets and Space
    The Man Who Made Wine - J.M. Scott
    The Man Who Ran Away - Dodson
  - Many - Modern (Box 20)
    Many Happy Returns
    Manzoni and His Times
    Margaret Tarrant Book
    Marshall Fields
    Me and Frumpet - Evans G. Valens
    Merrick, Leonard
    Merry Fiddlers
    Milne Pop up Book
    Mind of Light
    Miss Plum and Miss Penny - Dorothy Evelyn Smith
    The Mistress and Other Stories - Gina Berriault
    Mixed Train Daily
    Mocha, the Djuka by Johnson
    Modern Family Manners - Carolyn Hagner Shaw
    Modern Music Makers
  - Moon - Music (Box 20)
    Moon In My Pocket - Power-Waters
    The Moonflower Murder - Nichols
    More Marrels of Industrial Science - Capt. Burr Leyson
    Mother Penny by Robinson
    Mount Everst Reconnaissance
    Mr. Love and Justice - MacInnes
    Mr. Shakespeare of the Globe by Williams
    Mrs. Murphys Underpants - Fredric Brown
    Murder in Mind - Howard
    Murder Takes A Wife - James Howard
    The Museum Mystery - W.J. Campbell
    Music In History
  - My - Nathan (Box 20)
    My Best Friends Are Apes - Heinrich Oberjohann
    Mystery At Hurricane Hill
    My Brother Was An Only Child
    My Memories of Six Reigns - Princess Marie Louise
    Mystery of McClelland Creek - Wandy Jay Campbell
    Napolean and Mlle. George - Edith Saunders
    Nappy Planted A Garden by Hogan
    Nathan A Boy of Capernaum By Lillie
  - Nepal - Nine (Box 21)
    Nepal
    New Era of Flight
    The News Is Good
    Nicodemus and Gng by Hogan
    Nicodemus and Goose
    Nicodemus and Houn' Dog
    Nicodemus and His New Shoes
    Night and Hope
    Night Raider of the Atlantic
    Nine Man Eaters and One Rouge by Kenneth Anderson
  - No - Over (Box 21)
    No Idle Words and Having the Last Word by Brown
    None Shall Sleep Tonight
    No Picnic on Mt. Kenya
    O, The Brave Music by D.E. Smith
    O'Wiggins
    On Wings of Fire
    One For The Money by Lambert
    Only Lovers Left Alive by Wallis
    Options of Oliver Allston by Brooks
    Our Everst Adventure
    Our Town Has a Circus by McSwingan
    Out - Island Doctor Cottman w/ Blassingame
    Over The Reef by Gibbing
  - Paddlewheel - Party (Box 21)
    Paddlewheel Pirate - Newell
    Painted Lady - Faulkner
    Fall 1960 Paperbacks
    Paperbacks DEP - NGW Fall 1960
    Palace Diary
    Paloma by Mrs. Robert Henry
    The Parachute Greenwood Spring '64
    Party For Poodles
  - Patchwork - Peter (Box 21)
    Patchwork Kilt
    Patterns and Ceremonies by Meskowitz and Colher
    The Panses of the Eye - Knoll
    Peace With Honor by Milne
    Peacock on the Lawn
    Peddler in Paradise
    Pelican Prill
    Pemberley Shades by Bonaria-Hunt
    Peppercorn Days - Jon Rose
    Peter Hall by Davis
    About Peter Platypus - Hogan
  - Peter - Pictorial (Box 21)
    Peter Was a Pirate - Morse
    Phillips Brooks
    Pick of Punch 1956 - Bentley
    Pick of Punch 1957 - Bentley
    Pick of Punch 1958 - Bentley
    Pick of Punch 1959 - Bentley
    Picolo Pomi by Beltramelli
    The Pictorial Baseball Instructor
    Pictorial History of Texas - Mrs. Grambrell
  - Picture - Police (Box 21)
    Pictures of Everest
    Pidgy's Surprise - Jeanne Mellin
    Pinafore (H.M.S.) - Wheeler
    Pink Maple House
    Pipkin Sees The World
    Pirates of Penzance
    Pirandello Copyright
    Pixie on the Postoad by Wilson
    Plastics in the World of Tomorrow
    Platypus at Large - Kelen
    Plays for High Holidays by Tobitt and White
    Plotters by Carlson
    Poems and the Spring of Joy by Webb
    Police State by Thompson
  - Poligraphic - Portrait (Box 21)
    Poligraphic Co. of America
    Pocket Dictionary
    Pony Duet by Nancy Caffrey
    Poodle and the Sheep by Brown
    Pope Pius XII by Lenn and Reardon
    Pope Pius XII
    Popo's Miracle by Simon
    Portrait of Barry by Cynthia Asquith
  - Power - Professional (Box 21)
    Power of Karma
    Practically Perfect
    Practical Mysticism - Underhill
    Practical Yoga: Ancient and Modern
    The Praetonians - Jean Larteguy
    Preparing for Marriage
    Primitive India
    Principles of Equitation
    Prisoner's Bluff
    Producing Amateur Entertainment
    Professional Amateur - Biography of C.F. Ketting - Boyd
  - Prophet - Rafferty (Box 21)
    Prophet of Progress - Boyd
    Protocol and the Peabodies
    Proud Citadel by Dorothy Evelyn Smith
    Proud Fortress - Aller Andrews
    Psychic Sense (The)
    The Queen's Blade by Norman A. Gillespie
    Questions Aoler People Ask - Henrietta Kish
    Quiet Corner
    Quiet Hour
    Raccoon Twins By Hogan
    Rafferty - White
  - Raft - Rebel (Box 21)
    Raft of Despair
    Rampant Refugee by Carlisle
    Rampart Street by Webber
    Rapture in My Rags - Hastings
    Readings In New Canaan History
    Read To Me Charlie by Hogan
    Read To Me About The Littlest Country by Hogan
    Real Enjoyment of Living
    Rebel Yell by Ernenwein
  - Rebels - Regency (Box 21)
    Rebels Ride Proudly by Ernewein
    Reckless, Pride of the Marines
    Recollections of Three Reigns
    Red Beret
    Red Pawns
    Red Petticoats
    Rediscovery of Morals by Link
    Reef by Wheeler
    A Regency Visitor
  - Rehearsal - Rich (Box 21)
    Rehearsal by Cannon
    Relentless Tide by Bonaria-Hunt
    The Reluctant Legionnaire
    Remember and Forget by Adams
    Report from Formosa
    Rescue Tug
    The Return of The Kid by Wayne
    Revolt of Mamie Stover
    The Rich Die Hard by Beverly Nichols
  - Richest - Riot (Box 22)
    The Richest American - Getty
    Riding High
    Rights and Writers - Zavin and Pilpel
    Ring Around Rosa
    Riot
  - Rise - Roundabout (Box 22)
    The Rise of Simon Lachaume
    Road I Know By White
    Road to Santiago
    Robeen by Robinson
    Robin on the Mountain
    Rocky Mountain Reader
    Rogue In Space
    Romance
    Romance of the Rose
    Romantic New Orleans by Tallant
    Romantic Rouge by Carswell
    Rope Crazy by Robertson
    Round of the Year by Strong
    Roundabout
  - Royal - Sailors (Box 22)
    Royal Road by Simon
    Ruby McCollum Woman in The Sewanne Jail
    Runaway Toys by Hogan
    Run, Killer, Run
    Russia and the United States by Sorokin
    Rustlers of the Owlhorns
    Rusty Carousal by Sylvin
    Saddle on a Cloud
    The Sage of Conudos - Lucien Marchal
    Sailing by Knight
    Sailors of Fortune by MacKenzie
  - Saint - Savage (Box 22)
    Saint Anthony of the Desert
    Saint Santa Claus
    Salt In Our Wounds
    Salome Goes to the Fair by Witty and Coomer
    Sand Against the Wind
    San Gennaro Never Says No by Marotta
    Saturday Evening Post Cartoons
    Sauce and Sensuality by Elizabeth Ayrton
    Saucy Sailor
    Savage Papua - Andre Dupeyrat
  - Savage - Search (Box 22)
    Savage Play
    Saw Screams of Scotland Yard: Bernard Spillsbury
    Scene from the Saddle - Nancy Caffrey
    Science in A Sacred Cow by Standen
    Science of Hypnotism by Cannon
    Scotch Whiskey by Robb
    Scotts' Book by Douglas
    Sreaming Mimi by Brown
    Sea Hawks of Empire by Baily
    Seadragon - Steele
    Search In Secret India by Bruton
  - Search - Self (Box 22)
    Search For the King by Vidal
    Searchlight of Peace Plans
    Season of Comfort by Vidal
    The Season of Flesh by Reece
    Sea Wyf
    The Secret of Barnegat Light
    Secret Path by Bruton
    Selected Poems by Kreymborg
    The Self Starting Wheel - Murray
  - Seraphine - Shanghai (Box 22)
    Seraphine Went Walking by Serrage
    Serene Cincinnatians by Harlowe
    Sergeant Chung Ming - Maeter
    Serge in Rachmaninoff by Gronowicz
    The Serpent's Bite - Arnothy
    Seven for a Secret by Webb
    Seven Men at Daybreak - Burgess
    Seven Thousand Islands
    Seventy Years of Life and Labor by Gompers
    The Shaggy Dog & Other Murders - Fredric Brown
    Shakespeare's Heraldry by Scott-Giles
    Shanghai Conspiracy
  - Shapers - Short (Box 22)
    Shapers of American Fiction by Snell
    She Had A Magic - Brian O'Brien
    Shining Rain by Welshimer
    Ship With Two Captains
    Ships of the US Merchant Marines by Farrington
    The Shocking History of Advertising
    Shocking Life by Sciaperelli
    Short Encyclopedia of Nurses
  - Silent - Sing (Box 22)
    Silent Investigations - John Makris
    Silver Saddles
    Sliverlock by Meyers
    Simplified Physics by Small and Clarke
    Sine Qua Non - Sine
    Sing For America by Wheeler
    Sing Morning Star
    Sing Your Way To Better Speech by Walsh
  - Sink - Small (Box 22)
    Sink 'Em All
    Sisters Livingston (The)
    A Sister of a Satyr - Angrzeyevski
    Six Gun Herritage by Brad Ward
    Skeleton in the Closet
    Skorzeny's Secret Missions
    The Sleep of Baby Filbertson & Other Stories - James Leo Herliney
    Sleep Without Armor by P. Shand Allfrey
    Slim Gourmet's Soup Book
    Small Flags Waving
  - Small - Some (Box 22)
    Small Moments
    Small Town D.A.
    Smuggler's Paradise
    The Snake Stomper
    The Snow Birch - John Mantley
    The Snow Filly - Mitchell
    Snow House
    Snowplow the Tried to Go South
    Society and the Homosexual
    So Cold, My Bed
    Soldiers of God
    Some Follow the Sea
  - Someone - Sound (Box 22)
    Someone from the Past - Margot Bennett
    Some of Justin - Richard Vaughn
    Son of Man
    Son of Oscar Wilde - Holland
    A Song of Joy and Other Poems - Reece
    Song of Roland (The)
    Song of Tomorrow
    Songs from Now We Are Six
    Sorry No Budget - Preston
    The Sound - Russell
    Sound of Silence
  - Sound - Squarcio (Box 22)
    The Sound of Spanish Voices
    The Sound of Surprise - Balliet
    Sound of Voices
    Sounding Summer (The)
    South America
    Southern Europe
    The Spell of the Desert
    Spirit
    The Spring of Civilization
    Spots
    Spring's Green Shadow by Cecily Mackworth
    Spurs From San Isidro
    Squarcio
  - Stage - Still (Box 23)
    Stage of Fools
    Stairway to a Street
    Stalin
    Star Dream
    Star Spangled Summer
    Starlight and Storm
    Starts and Destiny
    Statues
    Steamboat Round the Bend
    Steeple Chasing
    Still Digging
  - Stolen - Story (Box 23)
    Stolen Journey
    The Stolen Sphere
    Stop Dieting, Start Losing
    Stories to Begin On
    Stories to Shorten the Road
    Stormy Life - E. Heinkel
    The Story of Axel Munthe - Munthe and Uexkull
    The Story of Everest
    Story of Father Dominique Pire
  - Story - Stuck-up (Box 23)
    Story The Fiction of the Forties
    Story of Mrs. Murphy (The)
    Story of Old New York (The)
    The Story of Young Edwin Booth - Alma Power-Waters
    Stowaway From St. Tropez - Terrot
    Strange Evil
    Strange Lovers
    Strange Return
    Straw in the Sun
    Straw Wife
    Struggle Is Our Brother
    Stuck-Up Prince
  - Submarine - Sweet (Box 23)
    Submarine Sailor
    Substance of a Dream
    Summer So Called
    Sunday in Virginia
    Sunflight
    Superior Children through Modern Nutrition
    Superjet
    Surgeon's Fight to Rebuild Men
    Surpring Summer
    Suzanne in Belgium
    Sweet Cork of Thee
    Sweet Thames Runs Softly
  - Swiss - Tangerine (Box 23)
    Swiss Everest Expedition
    The Sycamore Warrior
    The Synthesis of Yogo - Aurobindo
    Table Near The Band (A)
    Tales from Anderson
    Tales of Two Bunnies
    Tales of the Uncanny and Supernatural
    Tale of A Wishing Shrimp by Vladimir
    Take Care of My Little Girl
    Taming of the Arts (The)
    The Tangerine
  - Teeny - They (Box 23)
    Teeny Gay
    Tellico Blue
    The Temple of the Spirit
    Ten Thousand Eyes - Richard Collier
    Texas Adoptions
    Textbook of European Musical Instruments
    That's My Story - Corrigan
    Theatre Street - Karsavina
    Thelwell Country
    There Is A River - Vaughan
    There You Are (but where are you?) - Robert Mirvish
    Thesaurus of English Words & Phrases - Browning
    They Fell From Gods Hands
  - They're - Those (Box 23)
    They're On the Way
    They Stood Alone
    They Walk Again
    This Happened To Me
    This Life Is Eternal
    This Is Sylvia
    This Land Fulfilled - Charles A. Bradly
    This Pounding Wheel
    This Time - This Tide
    Those Smith Kids
  - Three - Times (Box 23)
    Three's A Crowd - McSwigan
    Three Silly Kittens
    Three Plays
    Tibetian Marches - Andre Migot
    Tilly's Strange Secret
    The Time of Terror - White
    Time of Turning (A)
    Time Readers Recipe Books
    A Time to Go Home
    Tim's Fight for the Valley - Bailey
    Time of Melville and Whitman
  - To (Box 23)
    To Find A Killer - White
    To Hidden Depths - Tailliez
    Toil, Taxes and Trouble
    To Live As We Wish
    To My Brothers Everywhere - Lieberman
    Tonty of the Iron Hand
    Tony Sees It Through
    The Tortured Path
    Touched With Fire
    To An Unknown Lady
  - Tower - Trumpet (Box 23)
    The Tower In The Sky - Joy DeWeese-Wehen
    Town with the Funny Name
    Towser, The Sheep Dog
    Traffic In Innocents - Terrot
    Trained for Genius
    Travels
    Travels of Sammy the Turtle
    Treasure Beyond Red Mesa
    Treasure of Naples (The)
    Treasures Long Hidden
    Trial By Gunsmoke
    Trouble At Tall Pine - Brad Ward
    A True Story - Stephen Hudson
    Trumpet
  - Tubie's - Typee (Box 23)
    Tubie's Monument
    The Turf Cutters Donkey Kicks Up His Heels
    Turnspit Dog
    Twentieth Century Warfare
    27th Day
    The Twins of Old Flatbush
    Twin Seals
    Two Against The Amazon
    Two Came To Town
    Two on a Continent
    Typee
  - Under - Virginia (Box 23)
    Undercover
    Unobstructed Universe
    U.S. West, the Saga of Wells Fargo
    Vangaurd! The Story of Man-Made Satellite by Martin Caidin
    Vanishing Virginian (The)
    Vatican (The) - Pichon
    Virginia Reader
  - Voices - Wines (Box 23)
    Voices of the Evening
    Walker's Rhyming Dictionary
    Wayside Altars
    What Mad Universe
    Wheeler
    Whistle Down The Wind - Bell
    White Figure, White Ground - Hugh Hood
    Whoa, Matilda!
    The Wild, Blue Road
    The Wild Valley - Serern
  - Woman - Young (Box 24)
    Woman In The Polar Night
    Word In Your Ear (A)
    Wondrous Egg of Abou
    World of Werner Bischof - Bischof
    The Wrong Horse - Bassan
    The Yellow Fever - Jean Larteguy
    Young Hickory: The Book of President Polk
    Young Traveler in France
  - Book reviews (in envelopes), 1957-1959 (Box 24)
    All That Was Mortal David Dempsey October 27, 1958
    All Through The Night Richard Vaughan May 6, 1957
    American Foreign Affairs William Lytle Schurz March 27, 1959
    The Americanization Of Emily William Bradford Huie August 12, 1959
    Angels On Horseback and Elsewhere Thelwell April 30, 1958
    Antiques Treasury November 4, 1959
    Around And About Marchette Chute September 23, 1957
    Balthazar Lawrence Durrell August 25, 1958
    Best Sport Stories - 1959 Irving T. Marshall & Edward Ehre June 15, 1959
    The Big Dive Kendell Foster Crossen Jan. 12, 1959
    The Big Drum Elizabeth Boatwright Coker May 3, 1957
    Bitter Lemons - Folder II - 1st Folder missing 3/12/59 Lawerence Durrell January 13, 1959
    The Bitter Passion John W. Wadleigh March 6, 1959
    Black Spice Davenport Steward July 24, 1959
    The Blackbird In The Lilac James Reeves Feb. 27, 1959
    Blow The Man Down! Based on James H. Williams Arr. & Edited by Warren F. Kuehl April 30, 1959
    The Blue Cup And Other Stories B.J. Chute August 9, 1957
    The Blue Cup And Other Stories II B.J. Chute Aug. 9, 1957
    Buffalo Country Bob Duncan Feb. 28, 1959
    The Camp Followers Ugo Pirro January 8, 1958
    Carribean Cavalier Davenport Steward August 1, 1957
    The Centurions Jean Larteguy January 3, 1962
    The Centurions II
    Challenge Of The Unknown Ed. by Sir Edward Hillary September 22, 1958
    The Charlatan Christine Arnothy August 28, 1959
    A Child'S GRACE Preface & verses by Ernest Claxton
    Photographs by Constance Bannister
    1948 and new printing Spring 1957
    Christian Dior And I by Christian Dior Sept. 25, 1957
    Circus Magic Versus by Sharon Banigan, Pictures by Katharina Millard Sept. 15, 1959
  - Book reviews (in envelopes), 1958-1962 (Box 25)
    CLE Lawrence Durrell March 30, 1960
    CLE Lawrence Durrell (folder II)
    Come North With Me: An Autobiography Bernt Balchen Aug. 8, 1958
    Congressman From India D.S. Saund August 4, 1960
    Coronation Everest James Morri August 6, 1958
    Countdown For Tomorrow Martin Caidin March 1, 1958
    The Dark Labyrinth Lawrence Durrel Feb. 16
    The Dark Labyrinth I Lawrence Durrell
    Decade In Europe Barrett McGurn May 18, 1959
    Don't Grow Old - Grow Up! Dorthy Carnegie
    Drag Strip William Campbell Gault Sept. 30, 1959
    The Echo Song Rosalie Fry March 1962
    Education And Freedom Vice Admiral H.G. Rickover, USN Jan. 30, 1959
    Education And Freedom Folder II
    Education And Freedom Folder III
    The Eigth Day Of The Week Marek Hlasko Sept. 3, 1958
    The Eight Day Of The Week (Folder II)
    Esprit De Corps Lawrence Durrell Jan. 13, 1959
  - Book reviews (in envelopes), 1954-1963 (Box 26)
    Dutton Everyman Paperbacks:
    1st 10 Volumes Published Sept. 20, 1957
    2nd 10 Volumes Published April 18, 1958
    3rd 10 Volumes Published Sept. 30, 1958
    Everyman's Classical Atlas J.O. Thomso June 9 1961
    Everyman's Dictionary Of Pictoral Art (2 volumes) William Gaunt April 16, 1962
    Everyman's Library American Edition I
    Everyman's Library Standard Edition II 1959
    Everyman's Library Standard English Edition Spring & Fall 1955-1957 Crown Octavo
    Extra Special Janet Lambert April 30, 1963
    Exploring For Fun William Burns Sept. 29, 1961
    Fairy Tales Of Many Lands I 1st 4 volumes pub. Feb 16 1960 China, Germany, Ireland, Russia
    Fairy Tales Of Many Lands II pub. October 20, 1960 England, France, India, Mexico
    Fairy Tales Of Many Lands III Persia, Japan, Denmark, Greece
    The Fastest Man Alive Lt. Col. Frank E. Everest Feb. 18, 1958
    Force Of Liberty Leonard Falkner April 18, 1959
    Foundations Of Tibetan Mystecism Lama Anagarika Govinda Feb. 19, 1959
    Gladstone: A Biography (folder I) Sir Philip Magnus Dec. 10, 1954
    The Gobbling Billy Dynely James September 16, 1959
    The Graveyard Marek Hlasko September 3, 1959
    Greenwillow (2 folders) B.J.Chute May 1, 1956
    Howells (2 folders) VanWyck Brooks October 7, 1959
    The Improper Bohemians Allen Churchill May 1, 1959
    John Adams Foodarama Party Book Joan Admas April 6, 1959
    Justine (2 folders) Lawrence Durrell August 21, 1957
    Kindergarten: Your Child's Big Step Minnie Perrin Berson September 28, 1959
    Land Of The Lamas Peter Goullart October 26, 1959
    The Littlest Bear Inez Hogan April 30, 1959
    Live Till Tomorrow Carola Haas Auguat 30, 1955
  - Book reviews (in envelopes) (Box 27)
    London Tony Armstrong Jones August 15, 1959
    The Lovely Day Dorothy Evelyn Smith August 6, 1959
    The Meriweather File Lionel White November 27, 1959
    Miscell. Adult 1960
    Miss Plum And Miss Penny Dorothy Evelyn Smith Feb. 25, 1959
    Mountolive (2 folders) Lawrence Durrell March 23, 1959
    No House Limit Steve Fisher October 13, 1958
    A Pearl To India Vincent Cronin April 17, 1959
    Peter Townsend Burrelle's Clippings
    Pets At The White Carl Carmer September 28, 1959
    Preacher's Kids Grace Nies Fletcher October 2, 1958
    A Primer On Communism George W. Cronyn Feb. 18, 1957
    The Questions Girls Ask Marjorie Vetter & Laura Vitary May 11, 1959
    The Richest American (2 folders) J. Paul Getty March 7, 1960
    Russian-English, English-Russian Pocket Dictionary compiled by S.G. Zaimovsky, ed. A.V. Litvinov May 15, 1958
    The Road To Santiago Walter Starkie May 28, 1957
    Sappho: A Play In Verse Lawrence Durrell Sept. 5, 1958
    The Search For The Tassili Frescoes Henri Lhote Nov. 9, 1959
    The Self Starting Wheel William Murray June 13, 1960
    Sergeant Chung Ming Hans Maeter September 15, 1961
    The Serpent'S BITE Christine Arnothy August 16, 1961
    The Slient Hostage Sarah Gainham August 12, 1960
    The Silent Investigators John N. Markis April 27, 1959
    The Silent Investigators (duplications)
    The Sleep Of Baby Filbertson And Other Stories James Leo Herlihy Jan. 8, 1959
    Small Women Alan Burgess (original folder missing) 1957
  - Book reviews (in envelopes) (Box 28)
    "Sorry No Budget" Charles Prestin November 15m 1960
    The Sound Ross Russell
    The Sound Of Surprise Whiteney Balliett August 6, 1959
    Spaceport U.S.A. Martin Caidin May 22, 1959
    Sports Of The Times Arthur Daley September 11, 1959
    Spread The Truth W.J. Granberg June 30, 1959
    Spillane, Mickey Miscellaneous newspaper and magazine comments - NOT REVIEWS
    Stiff Upper Lip Lawrence Durrell September 8, 1959
    The Stone Roses Sarah Gainham June 13, 1959
    Stowaway From St. Tropez Charles Terrot Sept. 29, 1960
    Stowaway To America Borghild Dahl March 30, 1959
    Successful Sure Fishing Jerry Jansen March 21, 1959
    Sunlight On The Lawn Beverly Nichols April 28, 1957
    Tale Of A Whistling Shrimp (2 folders) Vladimir B. Grinioff October 30, 1957
    The Tangerine Christine de Rivoyre March 11, 1959
    Those Without Shadows (2 folders) Francoise Sagan October 28, 1957
    The Treasured One Rudivoravan, Princess of Siam Nov. 1, 1957
    Tropical Aquarium Fish In Color G. Mandahl-Barth April 15, 1959
    Twenty Plus Two Frank Gruber February 13, 1961
    Twenty Seconds To Live Elizabeth Land October 6, 1959
    Twin Puppies Inez Hogan September 30, 1959
    Two Gentlemen (2 folders) Marchette Chute September 14, 1959
    The Valadon Drama John Storm March 2, 1959
    War For The Moon Martin Caidin Nov. 18, 1959
    Whistle Down The Wind Mary Hayley Bell August 12, 1959
    Willie Joe And His Small Change Marguerite Vance March 31, 1959
    The Wines Of Bordeaux J.R. Roger Dec. 12, 1960
    The Wrong Horse Jean Bassan Jan. 27, 1961
- Publicity files
  - Abbot - Adams (Box 29)
    Abbot, Eleanor Hallowell - Correspondence
    Abbott, Lyman - Letters to Mr. Dutton
    Abraham, J. Johnson - Surgeon's Log
    Abramowitz, Isidore
    Abraham, R.M.
    Acheson, Arthur
    Adams, Cleve F.
    Adams, F. - Adams, P.
    Adams, Florence
    Adams, Julia Davis
    Adams, Peter
  - Adams - Aksakov (Box 29)
    Addison, Rev. Charles Morris
    Affelder, Paul
    An Airman's Letter To His Mother (1941)
    Aksakov, Serge
  - Albee - Alexander (Box 29)
    Albee, Dr. Fred H.
    Aldington, Richard
    Alec - Tweedie, Mrs.
    Alexander, F. Matthias - Correspondence 1
  - Alexander I (Box 29)
    Alexander, F. Matthias - Correspondence 2
  - Alexander II (Box 29)
    Alexander, F. Matthias - Correspondence 3
    Alexander, F. Matthias - Bio, Photos, and Letters
    Alexander, F. Matthias - Reviews
  - Alexander - Almgren (Box 29)
    Alexander, Hartley
    Ali, A. Yussuf
    Allan, Doug - How To Write For Television
    Allan, H.W.
    Allen, Dr. A.V.G.
    Allan, Doug
    Allen, W.B. (1922-1931) (see Edward P. Dutton: Allen - Authors, Box 1, for 1897-8 correspondence)
    Almegren, Mrs.
  - Alsop - Aminoff (Box 29)
    Alsop, Gulielma F.
    American Book Prices Current
    Aminoff, Leonie
    Aminoff, Leonie - Old Reviews
  - Aminoff - Ambruster (Box 29)